是那种叫格雷的新毒品
It's the new drug called "Gray."
上周有两个人吸毒过量了
Two people OD'd on it last week.
知道是谁在经手吗
You know who's moving it?
不  还在查
No. Still working on it.
西恩娜  我要有用的情报
Sienna, I need something real
不然我只能起诉你非法持毒
or I have to file that coke possession charge.
我一直跟你说那不是我的
I keep telling you it wasn't mine.
-那家伙雇我...  -我相信你
- This guy paid me to-- - Yeah, I believe you.
所以我给了你一个月时间解决
Which is why I gave you a month to work it off.
现在还是什么都没有
So far, nothing.
你现在只剩三天
Now you only have three days left.
等等  等等  我还有别的
Wait, wait, wait, I've got something else.
我的朋友伊莎贝尔有时候会去俱乐部和我一起工作
My friend, Isabel--she works at the club with me sometimes.
她交了一个新男朋友
Anyway, she has this new boyfriend.
他会打她
He hits her.
真可怕  但是我们不处理家庭暴力案件
That's horrible, but we don't do domestic abuse cases.
谋杀呢
How about murder?
什么
What?
她说她男朋友杀过人
She said her boyfriend killed someone.
以前的女朋友  他把她打死了
An old girlfriend, he beat her to death.
所以我很担心伊莎贝尔
That's why I'm so scared for Isabel.
伊莎贝尔有没有说别的什么  名字之类的
Did Isabel say anything else--a name?
她就说她的男朋友把尸体扔在了一个工厂边上
She just said her boyfriend dumped the body near a factory.
-应该是怀亚特  -她男朋友是谁
- Wyatt, I think. - Who's the boyfriend?
她叫他D
She calls him D.
我没有追问细节
I didn't push for details.
我自己的麻烦够多了
Look, I've got enough drama of my own.
你上一次和伊莎贝尔说话是什么时候
When's the last time you talked to Isabel?
三周前
Three weeks ago.
我一直在给她发信息  但她没回过
I've been texting her, but she's not answering.
我不知道她住在哪里
And I don't know where she lives.
你复吸了  我看得出来
You're using again, I can see it.
-不  我没有  我发誓  -给你三天
- No, that's not true, I swear. - You have three days
给我点有用的  不然我就起诉
to find me something real or I file those charges.
-有什么好料吗  -没有
- She have anything good? - No.
说了一通她朋友的男朋友
I mean, some B.S. About her friend's boyfriend
杀了人  还抛尸在怀亚特工厂后之类的鬼话
killing someone, dumping the body behind the Wyatt factory.
她只是想争取点时间
She's just trying to buy more time
因为一个月时间快到了
because her month's almost up.
她看上去很难过
She looked pretty upset.
-没错  她是个好演员  -也许吧
- Yeah, she's a good actor. - Maybe.
也许还是值得上报的
It might still be worth calling in though.
不
No.
这说明你不打算
Does that mean you're not going
再给她点时间了吗
to give her any more time?
你不应该延长期限的
Well, you're not supposed to extend deals
规矩是这样
according to the book, so.
这是我第一个线人
This is my first C.I.
教程不一定都是对的
Yeah, the book's not always right.
有时候你得相信自己的直觉
Sometimes you got to trust your gut.
伍兹信了赃款的事
So Woods bought the money gag.
他以为我又是他的人了
Thinks I'm on his side again.
-很好  -那接下来怎么办
- All right, good. - Okay, so what's next?
我们什么时候拿下他
When do we take him down?
我们要找到他最大的弱点
We find his biggest weakness.
酒  女人  赌博
Booze, women, gambling.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
我已经找到了  老大  是你
I've already found it, boss. It's you.
谢了  亚当
Thanks, Adam.
翻译     小酸奶   风城章鱼X   Lynn_宁   H小欠
没事
Yeah.
翻译     小萝莉   不高兴童鞋   圈圈
还是不信
Still not convinced, huh?
不  我相信他  但这不代表我原谅他
No, I believe him. Doesn't mean I forgive him.
校对     圈圈
时间轴     chance-coco   西查
警长  有时间吗
Sarge, you got a minute?
后期     8T
我只是想为卡米拉的事道歉
I just wanted to apologize for what happened with Camilla.
总监     圈圈
是我让团队陷入糟糕的境地
I put the team in a bad situation.
很糟糕的境地  不会再出现那种情况了
A really bad situation, and it won't happen again.
我保证
You have my word.
在进一步通知下来之前  你不得出外勤
Well, you're on desk duty until further notice,
你下午一点得去见心理医生
and you've got an appointment with the psychologist at 1:00.
你真是太好了
Bless your heart.
双倍拿铁  三份糖
Double shot latte, three sugars.
我有没有告诉过你
Have I told you
你是我在情报组最喜欢的人
you're my favorite member of Intelligence?
从来没有
Never.
-你的  -谢了
- You. Mm-hmm. - Thanks.
西恩娜的事你决定了吗
Hey, so did you make a decision on Sienna?
嗯  她没有给我有用信息  我要起诉
Yeah. She doesn't deliver, I'm going to file the charges.
我给过机会  她搞砸了
I gave her a chance and she blew it.
很高兴看你也能硬气起来了
Ooh, nice to see you toughen up.
别让别人占你便宜了
Don't let anyone take advantage.
厄普顿警探
Detective Upton.
好的  我十分钟后到
Uh, yeah, I'll be there in 10 minutes.
-该走了  -什么  去哪里
- We got to go. - What? Where?
-谋杀案  -好吧
- Homicide. - Okay.
她好像是被打死的
Looks like she was beaten to death.
太残忍了
It's pretty gruesome.
谢谢你的跟进
Yeah. Hey, thanks for following up.
-很不错  -花了我50元呢
- Nice work. - It cost me 50 bucks.
为什么
How's that?
和温特斯赌十倍的赔率
Gave Winters over here ten-to-one odds
你的线人是在胡扯
your snitch was talking crap.
她的线人
Her snitch.
能帮个忙
Hey, can you do me a favor
去拉些警戒线吗
and make the appropriate notifications?
-好的  -谢了  伙计们
- Yeah. - Thanks, guys.
我说了  只是直觉
Like I said, it was just a hunch.
西恩娜的故事有点奇怪  不像是假的
Sienna's story was a little too weird to be fake.
-抱歉我僭越了  -没错
- I'm sorry if I overstepped. - You did.
至少你现在知道
Well, at least now you know
西恩娜不是在耍你了吧
Sienna isn't playing you, right?
芝加哥
警署
第五季
第十一集
这是一名无名死者
She's a Jane Doe.
我们提取了指纹  没找到结果
We ran her prints; they're not in the system.
我的线人也不知道她的名字
And my CI doesn't know her name either,
但她的朋友名叫伊莎贝尔·普雷兹
but her friend's name is Isabel Perez.
她在和这起凶案的嫌犯约会
And she's dating the same guy that looks good for this murder.
我们对她的信息掌握多少
What do we know about her?
-伊莎贝尔  -没错
- Isabel? - Yeah.
拉丁裔  21岁  以前会去
Latina, 21, used to work
西区的一家脱衣舞俱乐部工作
on and off at a strip club on the west side.
名叫不在场证明脱衣舞俱乐部
A place called Alibi.
我们觉得是她的男友杀了无名死者
Okay, so we think her boyfriend killed the Jane Doe?
没错  也许还有伊莎贝尔
Yeah, yeah, and maybe Isabel too.
因为她已经失踪了三周
Because she's been missing three weeks,
我试过追踪她的手机  关机了
I tried tracking her phone. It's dead.
好的  再去找你的线人谈谈
All right, well, talk to your C.I. again.
看看能有什么发现
See what you can find out.
同时  好好查查这名死者
Meanwhile, let's dig into this Jane Doe.
她叫什么  有什么故事
What's her name? What's her story?
需要我加入就告诉我
Let me know if you want me to jump in.
不  没关系
No, we're good.
你的预约在十分钟后
Your appointment's in ten minutes.
如果我是你  我可不想迟到
If I were you, I'd be on time.
我是丽贝卡·斯隆医生
I'm Dr. Rebecca Sloan.
以前来咨询过吗
Have you ever been in therapy before?
不久之前和别人谈过
Um, I talked to someone a while back, yeah.
-在开枪之后  -没错  那是强制的
- After a shooting. - Right, it's mandatory.
所以是你问我答吧
So, uh, so you ask me questions, and I talk, right?
这是你的时间
This is your time.
如果你有什么想谈的
If you have something you want to talk about,
我可以听
I'll listen.
如果我没有呢
And if I don't?
死因是钝器外伤
C.O.D. was blunt force trauma.
她被某种长棍状物体反复击打
She was beaten repeatedly with a long object,
比如铁管或者轮胎扳手之类的
like a pipe or a tire iron.
从平行的伤痕就能看出来
You can tell by the parallel tracks.
什么时候死的
When'd she die?
根据尸斑  大约一个月前吧
Based on decomp, about a month ago.
身体上有什么证据吗
Find any evidence on her body?
我正在做精液检测
I'm running semen samples now.
-性侵犯吗  -难说
- Sexual assault? - Hard to say.
没有组织撕裂
No tearing of tissues.
有没有防卫伤之类的
Any offensive or defensive wounds?
都没有  似乎她也没怎么挣扎反抗
No, doesn't look like there was much of a struggle.
她很可能认识凶手
Probably knew her killer.
这就和线人的说法对上了
That syncs up with the C.I. story,
男的杀了女友
boyfriend killed girlfriend.
还有一点值得注意一下
There's one other thing worth pointing out.
她做了不少整容手术
She's had lots of cosmetic procedures.
丰胸  美臀  丰唇之类的
Injections into the breasts, buttocks, lips.
好  那我们列一份附近整形医院的名单
All right, we'll get a list of nearby plastic surgeons.
很可能白费工夫
Probably a waste of time.
看上去她被注射了电机润滑油
It appears she was injected with motor oil.
所以这个伊莎贝尔的男朋友真的杀了人
So this guy Isabel is with really killed somebody?
-天啊  -看来是这样
- Damn. - Looks that way.
我们在怀亚特工厂后面找到了遗体
We found the body behind the Wyatt factory,
正如伊莎贝尔所说
just like Isabel said.
我庆幸我对你说了
I'm glad I told you about it.
我本来还不确定  伊兹常常说大话
I wasn't sure, you know, Izzy, she says a lot of wacky things.
但即便对她来说这也太过了
But this was crazy, even for her.
我可不能背上重罪的罪名
I can't have no felony on my record.
我以后也别想在餐厅找到工作了
I'll never get a good job at a restaurant.
我学过当厨师
I'm training to be a chef.
那很好  所以你集中精力
That's great. So just stay focused.
我需要你做什么就做  你不会有事的
Do what I need you to do, and you'll be fine.
先从一开始说吧
Let's start at the beginning, okay?
伊莎贝尔在遇到D之前住在哪
Where was Isabel living before she met D?
庇护所  一家慈善机构之类的
A shelter. Like a charity thing.
就是有床有顾问和吃的那种
You know, beds, counselors, food.
伊兹一直想把生活推上正轨
Izzy was always trying to get her life right.
只不过一直没机会
She just never could.
那里叫什么
What's it called?
没有  没怎么见过她
No, she doesn't look familiar.
但我们每月和超过一百位女士谈过话
But we talk to over a hundred women a month.
其中许多都很羞于见人
Many of them are timid,
或者太害怕  都不肯告诉我们真名
or so scared they won't even tell us their real names.
但我们还是接纳了她们
But we let them in nonetheless.
这是什么案子
What's this about?
她失踪了
She was reported missing.
我们能检查下你这里的档案吗
Can we look through some of your files?
当然  我可以帮你们
Yeah, of course. Yeah, I can help with that.
太好了  多谢你  胡安
Great. Thanks, Juan.
好吧  你说得对
Okay, you're right.
伊莎贝尔·普雷兹  就是她
Isabel Perez, here she is.
原来她来过好几次了
Turns out she's been here several times.
她上次来是什么时候
Well, when was the last time she was here?
两个月前
Two months ago.
阿曼达给她做了咨询
All right, Amanda was her counselor.
阿曼达
Amanda.
警察来问一个伊莎贝尔·普雷兹的情况
The police are asking about someone named Isabel Perez.
怎么了  她出什么事了吗
Why, did something happen to her?
我们还不确定
We're not sure.
我们只想问几个问题
We just want to ask a few questions.
好  说真的  我正希望你们来呢
Sure. Truth is, I'm glad you're here.
我一直很担心她
I've been worried about her.
我一直在联系她  发短信
I've been calling and texting her--
你上次和她联系是什么时候
When was the last time you heard from her?
大约三个星期前吧
About three weeks ago.
她有没有说什么异常的话
Did she say anything unusual?
有没有难过  开心或者低落
Did she seem sad, happy, upset?
更像是兴奋
More like excited.
她正要去接受整形手术
She was on her way to get cosmetic surgery.
好像是要做美臀吧
An injection in her buttocks, I think.
我挺难过的  她这么年轻漂亮
Made me sad. She's so young and pretty,
但是她男友一直催她去做手术
but her boyfriend really wanted her to do it
她也想讨男友欢心
and she wants to make him happy.
伊莎贝尔说过她男友叫什么吗
Did Isabel tell you the name of her boyfriend?
那整形医生呢  诊所名称呢
What about the doctor, or the clinic?
都没有  抱歉
No, sorry.
好吧  如果你有她的回音
Okay, well, if you hear from her,
请联系我
you call me.
当然  如果你们
Absolutely, and please call
还有别的问题  就打电话
if you have any other questions.
-好  -多谢
- Yeah. - Thanks.
见到你很高兴  劳尔  怎么了
Good to see you, Raul. What's up?
玛丽亚做了奶酪卷
Maria made cheese tamales.
拜托  别跟我说这也违规吧
Oh, come on, don't tell me they're against the rules.
-我知道你爱吃  -的确  谢谢
- I know you love them. - I do, thank you.
我也希望能给你提供些情报
I wish I had something to tell you, Herma,
但是生意最近不太好
but business has been soft.
有两个月没开新药房了
Haven't installed a drug compartment in two months.
我是来和你谈些别的事的
I came to talk to you about something else.
有个杀人案  二十来岁的年轻女性
There was a murder. Young woman, twenties.
杀人案  这我可应付不来
Oh, a murder? Hell no, that's not for me.
我向你提供毒贩子藏在车里的
Listen, I tell you about hidden compartments
隐藏流动药房  这是我们约好的
in narco's cars. That's our deal.
我不是来和你谈凶杀案本身的
All right, I didn't come to talk to you about the murder.
我只是想问问你知不知道
I just wanted to know if you know of
皮尔森有没有什么地下诊所
any off-the-books medical clinics in Pilsen.
就是那种给女性做整形手术的
Somewhere that women go to get plastic surgery, injections.
你就在这一带混  我想你可能知道些什么
It's your hood, I figured you might know something.
这就简单了  让我去打听打听
Yeah, that's easy. Let me ask around.
那好 多谢
Okay, great. Thank you.
-好的  -代我谢谢玛丽亚的奶酪卷
- All right. - Thank Maria for the tamales.
好的
I will.
有好消息了
We got good news.
这个无名女的身份有结果了
We got a positive ID on the Jane Doe.
她的名字是希尔维亚·卡斯特罗
She goes by the name of Sylvia Castro.
我们去伊莎贝尔工作过的脱衣舞俱乐部问过
We stopped by the strip club that Isabel used to work at.
原来希尔维亚也在那里工作过
It turns out Sylvia worked there too.
老板认出了犯罪现场的照片
Boss ID'd the crime scene photo,
但他完全不知道她还有个男友
but he did not know anything about a boyfriend.
好  我们还知道什么
Okay, what else do we know?
我们知道她19岁  来自克利夫兰
We know she's 19, originally from Cleveland,
已经失踪了三个月没来上班了
and she's been missing from work for about three months.
好  找到她的家人
All right, track down the family
给他们通报情况
and let them know what happened.
好  去找希尔维亚的朋友同事和室友谈谈
All right, talk to Sylvia's friends, co-workers, roommates.
肯定有人知道这个男友是谁
Someone's got to know who this boyfriend was.
你确定就是这吗
Are you sure this is it?
劳尔给我的地址就是这里
It's the address Raul gave me.
看起来不像是个医疗诊所
Doesn't look like a medical clinic.
我想这才是重点
I think that's the point.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
-该走了  女士  -给我
- Time to go, ma'am. - Give me that.
别回来了  这不是个真正的医生
Don't come back. This isn't a real doctor.
不  不是  我从没说过我是真正的医生
No, no, I never said I was a real doctor.
我不做手术  我不做手术  我只是...
I don't operate, I don't do surgery, I just--
你只是给女人注入发动机油
You just inject women with motor oil.
我们在找你的一位病人
We're trying to find one of your patients.
认识她吗
Recognize her?
认识  伊莎贝尔  我记得她姓普雷兹
Yeah. Isabella, I think her last name is Perez.
好  那她的男朋友呢
Okay, what about her boyfriend?
你知道他的名字吗
Do you know his name?
不知道
No.
那她呢  你认识她吗
What about her, you recognize her?
她也是你的病人
She was one of your patients.
她叫希尔维亚·卡斯特罗
Her name was Sylvia Castro,
她和伊莎贝尔的男朋友是一个人
same boyfriend as Isabel.
她们的男朋友的名字是什么
We want a name now.
鉴于这里发生的一切
And given what's going on here,
你应该想要配合我们的工作的
you're going to want to cooperate.
因为你会需要你能得到的所有帮助
Because you're going to need all the help you can get.
警长  刚刚和死者的妹妹谈过了
Hey, Sarge, just talked to our DOA's sister.
在她遇到她神秘的男友之前
Right before she met this mystery boyfriend,
她住在一个叫珍妮避风港的地方
she was living in a shelter called Jenny's Haven.
等等
Wait.
-你是说珍妮避风港  -是的
- Did you say Jenny's Haven? - Yeah.
伊莎贝尔也在那里待过
That's the same place Isabel stayed at.
现在伊莎贝尔和我们的死者
That's now two things
有两个相同点了
Isabel and our DOA have in common.
他们都在同一家地下诊所做了整形手术
They both got plastic surgery at the same underground clinic.
付钱的是同一个人  达米安·索托
Paid for by the same guy, Damien Soto.
找到了  有两次前科
Yeah, I got him right here. Two priors.
一次是殴打和侵犯人身  一次是拉皮条
One for assault and battery, one for pandering.
那么他是个拉皮条的
Oh, so he's a pimp.
有这混蛋的照片吗
We got a photo of this prick?
好的  等一下
All right, give me one sec.
那是胡安  是珍妮避风港的人
That's Juan. From Jenny's Haven.
你是说这家伙在庇护所工作
You're telling me this guy works at the shelter?
不  他是创办者
No, he's the founder.
真是让狐狸看鸡窝
That's a fox guarding the henhouse.
好了  把这孙子抓回来
All right, grab this son of a bitch now.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
厄普顿
Upton.
往前
Go forward.
-安全  -我去厨房
- Clear! - I got the kitchen.
安全
Clear.
三张空床
Three empty beds.
-他们是匆忙离开的  -是啊  是谁告的密
- Well, they left in a hurry. - Yeah, who tipped them off?
看来不仅仅是伊莎贝尔
Looks like Isabel wasn't his only girl.
你是说囚犯  他把他们关在这里
You mean prisoner. He's locking them up.
5021E  叫取证室到水街540号
5021 Eddie, roll the crime lab to 540 Water Street.
我们需要提取现场的指纹
We need a scene processed for prints.
收到  5021E
Copy that, 5021 Eddie.
伯吉斯
Burgess.
15分钟内赶到
I'll be there in 15.
伙计们  我们走吧
Hey, guys, we're going to break off.
收到
Yeah, copy that.
你朋友昨晚在拉辛大道看到了伊莎贝尔
So your friend saw Isabel on Racine Avenue last night?
是的  大概在午夜的时候
Yeah, around midnight.
-她和一个人在一起  -干什么
- She was with some guy. - Doing what?
不知道  但我猜是在搞毒品
Don't know, but I'm guessing looking for dope.
她有毒瘾  我一直在努力帮她
She's got to have it, and I've been trying to help her,
-但...  -至少你知道她还活着
- but-- - Well, at least you know she's still alive.
-这才是最重要的  对吗  -是
- That's something, right? - Right.
现在我们只需要带她远离她那糟糕的男友
Now we just need to get her away from that awful boyfriend.
你是说那个拉皮条的  他叫达米安·索托
Uh, you mean pimp. His name is Damien Soto.
他手下还有六个女孩
He's got six other girls, too.
真恶心
Makes me sick.
你说伊莎贝尔吸毒
You said Isabel has a drug habit.
也就是说她没多久就得出来买毒品
That means she'll be looking to score sometime soon.
所以你四处问问  看看谁见过她
So why don't you ask around, see who's selling to her.
这样我们就能找到她了
We'll track her down that way.
在皮尔森社区四处走动  和海洛因毒贩交谈
Walk around Pilsen talking to heroin dealers?
不  我不吸毒
Nah, I'm clean.
我不喜欢在那片区域游晃
I don't like hanging out in that area.
是啊  那的确很危险
Yeah, that's dangerous, no doubt.
西恩娜  我们说好的
Sienna, we had a deal.
我说的是如果你帮我找到凶手
I said if you help find the killer,
我就不提起指控
I wouldn't file charges.
目前为止  你还没有帮到什么
So far, you haven't done much helping.
你可真冷血
Wow. That's pretty hardcore.
别搞砸了  你在上烹饪课
Don't blow it. You're taking cooking classes.
你那么努力想当一个厨师
You're working hard to be a chef.
特别努力  而且我学得很好
Real hard. And I'm good, too.
无所谓的  如果你不合作
It doesn't matter. If you don't cooperate,
你就只能在州重刑监狱烹饪了
the only place you'll be cooking is Stateville.
好了  好了  我会试试的
Okay, okay, I'll give it a shot.
很好
That's a good choice.
这是500块  给毒贩
Here's 500, grease the dealers.
告诉他们如果能提供线索的话可以拿到更多
Tell them there's more cash if they deliver a lead.
我不准备告诉你怎么做你的工作
Look, I'm not going to tell you how to do your job,
但那的确很冷血
but that was pretty hardcore.
她是个线人  海莉  那是她的工作
She's a C.I., Haley. That's what she signed up for.
我查了拉丁报纸
So I figured I'd check out the Latino papers,
看看那皮条客有没有打过广告
and staysee if this pimp fraud's was advertising.
看看我找到了什么
Look what I found.
那绝对是伊莎贝尔
That is definitely Isabel.
那就给他们打电话  我们去把她抓回来
So call them, we'll go grab her up.
我已经打过了  打不通
I already did. The phone's been disconnected.
网站也关了
The website's down too.
他很聪明
Oh, he's smart.
在风声过去之前夹着尾巴生活
Staying under the radar until the heat dies down.
我和珍妮避风港的三位现住户
I talked to three current residents
和七位过去的住户谈过
and seven past residents of Jenny's Haven.
其中有一个16岁的小女孩
One of the girls was 16.
达米安给他买珠宝  带她吃晚餐
Damien buys her jewelry, takes her out to dinner.
他像金子一样供着她们
What he does is he treats them like gold,
再把他们卖给出价最高的人
then turns them out to the highest bidder.
是的  如果他们不好好做的话
Yeah, and if they get out of line,
他就用卸胎棒把他们打死
he just beats them to death with a tire iron.
取证组在达米安的房子里
The crime lab pulled eight sets of prints
找到了八组指纹
from Damien's house,
但只有达米安的指纹是记录在案的
but the only match is to Damien.
我们还想
And we also managed
查一下达米安的车辆信息
to pick up Damien's vehicle information.
好  立刻发通缉令
All right, put out a BOLO right away.
同时  到街上转转
In the meantime, hit the streets.
把他的照片贴出去
Get his picture out there.
达米安·索托  不认识
Damien Soto? Never heard of him.
我们认为他在皮尔森的某个地方做着点小生意
We think he runs a small operation somewhere in Pilsen.
我不太关注这些
I don't pay much attention to the mom and pops.
这家伙并不是什么热情友好的人
This guy isn't exactly warm and fuzzy.
他用卸胎棒杀了手下一个姑娘
He killed one of his girls with a tire iron.
真希望我能帮忙  汉克  但我不混那边
I wish I could help, Hank. But I don't run in that crowd.
这你也知道
You know that.
我这都是高学历的优质姑娘
My girls are high-end, educated.
她们做这事是因为自己想做
They do what they do because they want to.
帕特丽夏  我来不是为了评判
Patricia, I'm not here to judge.
我只是想求助
I'm just trying to get some help.
我知道  抱歉
I know, sorry.
那我问你
So let me ask.
那样一个人
Okay, a guy like that.
一个在逃的皮条客  不敢让他的姑娘工作
You know, a pimp on the lam afraid to work his girls.
那他怎么赚钱
How does he make his money?
他既然不能拉皮条  就贩卖她们咯
Well, he can't pimp them, he'll sell them.
很冷血  但那些人就是这么干的
It's cold-blooded, but that's how these guys roll.
谢谢
Thanks.
对了
And by the way.
你觉得妮可怎么样
How do you like Nicole?
她挺好的
She's nice.
她说你们两个就纯聊天
She says you two just talk.
跟心理辅导似的
Like it's a therapy session or something.
快说你们有线索了
Please tell me you got a lead.
我们一直在看
Well, we've been going through
所有的监控录像
all the surveillance footage we can,
但还是一无所获  所以
but we're still coming up empty, so.
-达米安的电话有料吗  -没有  长官
- Any luck with Damien's phone? - No, sir.
车上也没线索
And no hit on the car, either.
他总得找时间出来透透气
Right, well, he has got to come up for air at some point,
-所以继续盯着  -没问题  老大
- so stay on it. - You got it, boss.
我在附近安排了全天候流动巡逻
I've got patrol canvassing the neighborhood 24/7.
好的  谢谢  你线人那里有回复吗
All right, thanks. You get word from your C.I.?
有  我几个小时前跟她聊过
Yeah, I talked to her a few hours ago.
她找到一个毒贩
She found a dealer
两天前卖过海洛因给伊莎贝尔
who sold Isabel heroin two days ago.
说伊莎贝尔再找他买就给她发信息
Said he'd text her again when Isabel was looking to score.
-很好  -是的
- Nice. - Yeah.
伯吉斯
Burgess.
什么
What?
什么时候
When?
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
就在这里  胸口中了两枪
It's just down here. Shot twice in the chest.
她手机的近期通话记录里有你的号码
Found your number in her cell on the recently called list.
-她叫...  -西恩娜
- Her name is-- - Sienna.
我知道  她是我的线人
I know, she's my informant.
巡警在现场发现了西恩娜的手机
Patrol has found Sienna's phone at the scene.
她昨晚十点十二分收到毒贩的短信
She had a text message from the drug dealer last night at 10:12,
说他会跟伊莎贝尔在公园见面
saying he was meeting up with Isabel in the park,
我们就是在公园找到了她的尸体
same place we found the body.
会是抢劫吗
Could be a robbery?
不会  她口袋里有钱包
No, she had her wallet in her pocket.
里面也有现金
She had some cash in there, too.
这是陷阱
It was a setup.
毒贩发信息给达米安  达米安杀了她
The dealer texted Damien, Damien killed her.
他不想让任何人妨碍他的生意
He didn't want anyone getting in the way of his business.
好  这个毒贩我们有什么线索
Okay, what do we know about this dealer?
爱德华多·瓦雷拉
Eduardo Varela.
两条前科  分销海洛因
Two priors, heroin distribution.
我们也有他的地址  胡佛路134号
We have his address, too. 134 Hoover Road.
去拜访一下爱德华多
So pay Eduardo a visit.
给他施压  给我答复
And squeeze him. I want answers.
好的
Yeah.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Hey, you all right? - Yeah.
西恩娜的事我很遗憾  但是...
Listen, I'm sorry about Sienna, but...
这不是你的责任
You know, that's not on you.
我觉得我逼她太紧了
I think I pushed too hard.
不  不是这样
No, that's how it goes.
这只是职责所在  好吗
You were doing your job, okay?
你不犯人  人会来犯你
You're either playing or you're getting played.
我们去跟这个海洛因毒贩聊聊吧
Okay, let's go talk to this heroin dealer.
好吗
All right?
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
-你是爱德华多·瓦雷拉吗  -什么情况
- Hey, you Eduardo Varela? - What's going on?
滚开别挡道
Move your punk ass out the way!
你无权这样对我说
You have no right talking to me like that.
别这么跟我说话  艾迪
Hey, don't talk to me like that, Eddie,
我现在心情不好  转身  手举起来
'cause I'm not in the mood. Turn around, get your hands up.
举起来
Hands up!
可以了
We're good.
好  坐下
All right, sit down.
你坐下
Have a seat.
达米安·索托在哪里
Where's Damien Soto?
不认识这个人
Don't know nobody with that name.
哥们  我们没时间跟你废话
Dude, we don't got time for that.
我们知道你见过西恩娜之后
We know you just got off the phone with him
就跟他打过电话
right after you met with Sienna.
然后你给她发了条短信  现在她死了
And then you sent her a text, and now she's dead.
总得有人背这个锅  艾迪
Somebody's got to answer for that, Eddie.
看看我们找到了什么
Look what we found.
海洛因啊  这可不出奇
Oh, heroin, huh? I'm not surprised.
你有两个选择  爱德华多
You have two choices, Eduardo.
一  我们以私藏海洛因罪
One, we bust you for heroin possession
和蓄意谋杀罪逮捕你
and conspiracy to commit murder.
二  你帮我们找到伊莎贝尔·普雷兹
Or two, you help us find Isabel Perez.
达米安·索托那混蛋也行  这取决于你
Or Damien Soto's bitch ass. It's up to you.
好吧  好吧  我认识他
Okay, okay. I know who he is.
我也认识伊兹  但我没有帮忙杀人
And I know Izzy, but I didn't help get no one killed.
我不会干那种事
That's not what I'm about.
对  因为你在主日学校讲课
Right, because you teach Sunday school.
达米安叫我发那条短信
Damien told me to send that text
让伊莎贝尔能跟她朋友聊聊
so Isabel could talk to her friend.
告诉我们达米安·索托在哪里
Tell us where Damien Soto is.
我不知道
I don't know.
但我知道过几个小时
But I do know that Izzy's coming over
伊兹会过来拿货
in a few hours to score some product.
也没那么难  是吧  艾迪
All right, that wasn't that hard, was it, Eddie?
现在你要假装一切正常
Now, you're going to pretend like everything's normal
其它的交给我们
and let us do our job.
好的  那之后呢
Okay. What happens after that?
你给我当线人  不然你就去监狱待着
You work for me as an informant or you go to jail.
安东尼奥  现在知道他怎么有这么多线人了
Antonio, man--now I know why he's got so many C.I.'s.
一有机会他就提要求
He sees the opportunity, he just makes the ask.
是吧  我们都在场
Right? I mean, we were all there.
我觉得爱德华多应该算是团队线人之类的
I feel like Eduardo should be a group C.I. or something.
我不明白怎么就归安东尼奥一个人了
I mean, I don't understand how Antonio gets dibs.
因为是他说的
Because he asked.
注意
Hey, look out.
目标到了
The target has just arrived.
是一个不认识的司机  我们看不清
It's an unknown driver. We can't really tell.
伊莎贝尔归我们  司机归你们
We'll take Isabel, you take the driver.
收到
Copy that.
我只有四十块  但我...
I only have $40 bucks. But I--
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
没关系  没关系  你没事
Hey, hey, it's okay, it's okay, you're not in trouble.
我们是来帮你的
We're here to help.
下车
Get out the vehicle.
把手放到我能看到的地方
Put your hands where I can see them.
关掉引擎  现在就关掉
Turn off the car. Turn off the car now!
不许动  不许动
Hey! Do not move. Do not move.
-该死  -妈的
- Damn! - Son of a bitch!
追追追
Go, go, go, go, go!
听好
Listen.
事先说清楚
Look, just to be clear...
我们不想起诉你
We don't want to press charges against you, okay?
你现在住哪儿
Where are you living right now?
房子里  但我不知道确切地址
In a house. But I don't know where it is.
我没注意
I don't pay attention.
你男朋友是达米安对吧
Your boyfriend. This is Damien, hm?
我们得和他聊聊
We need to talk to him.
为什么
How come?
他可能杀了一个叫希尔维亚·卡斯特罗的年轻女人
We think he killed a young woman named Sylvia Castro.
还有你朋友西安娜
And your friend, Sienna.
什么
What?
没错
Yeah.
西安娜死了
S-Sienna's dead?
昨晚死的
Died last night.
达米安对着她胸口连开两枪
Damien shot her in the chest twice.
她试着去找你  想帮你
She was trying to find you. She was trying to help you.
昨晚  达米安衣服上有血迹吗
Last night, did Damien have blood on his clothes?
手上  鞋子上
Hands? Shoes?
伊莎贝尔  你其他室友有危险
Isabel, the other girls you live with are in danger.
她们需要你的帮助
They need your help.
抱歉  我什么也不记得
Sorry, I don't remember anything.
给我们点时间  出来  金
Give us a minute. Come on, Kim.
从她嘴里我们不会得到任何关于昨晚的信息
We're not going to get anything out of her tonight.
得为她的戒断提供一些什么
I think we should just give her something for her withdrawal,
把她带到我们的安全屋
put her up in one of our safe houses,
让她休息一下
let her get some rest.
明天再审一下她
We'll take another run at her tomorrow.
好的
Okay.
还是没找到司机或车
Still haven't found the driver or the car.
抱歉  老大
I'm sorry, boss.
他比我们设想的提前露面
He showed up earlier than we thought.
厄普顿和奥林斯基还没到现场
Upton and Olinsky hadn't arrived yet,
不过我们通过无线电台发布他的牌号了
but we put the plates out over the radio.
在等线索
Just waiting on a hit.
你晚上还有活儿
Well, your night isn't over.
我想让你和金帮伊莎贝尔安排妥当
I want you to go with Kim, help get Isabel squared away.
明白
Copy that.
不会有人知道你在这里
All right, no one knows you're here.
除非你在猫眼里看到带警徽的人
Don't open the door unless you look through the peephole
否则别开门
and you see a badge, all right?
我给你带了换洗衣服
I brought you a change of clothes.
洗过澡你会感觉好很多
You'll feel better after a shower.
需要任何东西  用这个电话打给我们
And, um, if you need anything, you use this phone to call us.
好的  谢谢
Oh, okay. Thank you.
不客气
Yeah.
这附近会有警察巡逻吗
So, um, will there be any police around?
对  前面会有辆巡逻车
Yeah, there will be a patrol car out front.
你在这里一个人可以吗
Do you feel all right in here by yourself?
没事的
Yeah, I'm fine.
-我觉得很安全  -那就好
- I-I feel safe. - Good. You are.
安排好了
All right, you're all set.
走之前  再问你一遍
Listen, before we go, I've got to ask you again.
达米安在哪儿  他住哪儿
Where's Damien? Where's he staying?
亚当  别问了行吗
Adam, would you just stop? Would you stop?
停下  她还没准备好
Stop. She's not ready.
没事的  好好休息  好吗
You're okay. Get some rest, okay?
她为什么要保护那混蛋
Why is she protecting that son of a bitch?
我不明白
I don't get it.
因为她爱他
Because she's in love with him.
爱
In love with him?
-对  -那不是爱
- Yeah. - That's not love.
是斯德哥尔摩综合症
That's Stockholm Syndrome.
试着告诉她那不是爱
Try telling her it's not love.
有时候人
Sometimes people...
会自欺欺人  相信自己想要相信的
They trick themselves into believing what they want to believe,
因为那会比真实情况感觉更好
because it feels better than the alternative.
不过有些时候确实是真实情况
Well, sometimes it's real.
不是自欺欺人或幻觉
And there's no tricks or delusions.
那就很好
It's just good.
也许很复杂  但是很诚实
It might be complicated, but it's honest.
-拜托  -不知道把电话给她
- Oh, come on. - I don't know if leaving the phone
是不是个好主意  金
was a really good idea, Kim.
不知道她会不会上钩
I just, I don't know if she's going to take the bait.
无论她爱不爱他
Whether she loves him or not,
她都很怕他
she's terrified of the guy.
等等  她打电话了
Hold on, she's making a call.
-达米安  是我  -你在哪  宝贝
- Damien, it's me. - Where are you, baby?
我担心你很久了
I've been so worried about you.
警察把我关在安全屋
The police have me in a safe house.
他们在那儿吗
Are they there?
不  他们离开了
No, they left.
好  我来接你  不过以防万一
Okay, I'll come get you. But just in case,
和我在几个街区外碰面
meet me a few blocks away.
好  和我在欧文街和15大道之间的小巷碰面
Okay, meet me in the alley between Irving and 15th.
20分钟后到
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
-爱你  达米安  -我也爱你  宝贝
- I love you, D. - I love you too, baby.
漂亮
Nice.
伊莎贝尔刚刚和达米安·索托联系了
Isabel just made contact with Damien Soto.
我们有她拨打的号码  我现在就打过去
We have the number she dialed. I'm calling it in now.
我需要人帮我定位  尽快
I need someone to ping it, ASAP.
收到  待命
Copy that. Standing by.
如我所说  这是个好主意
Well, like I said, it was a good idea.
有个西班牙裔男性  从东边过来
That's a male Hispanic, approaching from the east.
-行动  -好的
- Let's go. - Okay.
你还好吗
Hey, you good?
是的
Yeah.
芝加哥警署
Chicago PD!
-你设计我  婊子  -没  别开枪
- You set me up, you lying whore! - No, no, don't shoot.
-放下武器  -我没告诉他们
- Drop your weapon! - I didn't tell them!
放下武器
Drop your weapon!
-好枪法  -不不
- Nice shot. - No, no!
-伊莎贝尔  -我不知道他们在  我发誓没设计你
- Isabel.  - I didn't know they were here. I swear I didn't set you up.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
你们在这里干嘛  为什么开枪打他
What are you doing here? Why did you shoot him?
-别死  我爱你  -我是1521F  紧急情况
- Please don't die, I love you. - 1521, Frank emergency.
警方开枪  疑犯中枪
Shots fired by the police. Offender down.
-别伤害他了  求你们  -没事的  呼吸
- Stop hurting him, please... - You're okay, just breathe.
我们在西欧文街4200号的巷子里
4200 West Irving, we're in the alley.
为什么那么做
Why would you do that?
收到
Copy that.
深呼吸
Just breathe.
不
No.
达米安肩部中了两枪
Damien took two to the shoulder.
现在在动手术  不会死的
He's in surgery right now. He's going to live.
好  伊莎贝尔呢
All right, where's Isabel?
安东尼奥把她带去诊所了  她现在不太好
Antonio took her to a clinic. She's in bad shape.
在戒断阶段还看到达米安中枪
Between the withdrawals and seeing Damien get shot,
她已经崩溃了
she's a mess.
好  那那通电话呢
Okay, well, what about the phone call?
查到位置了吗
We got a location?
嗯  信号来自于南部一家名叫
Yeah, pinged off a cell tower on the south side,
维尼的酒吧附近的信号塔
near a bar named Vinnie's.
那里的服务员证实了10点到11点他一直在那里
The waitress there confirmed he was there from 10 to 11.
我查过他的手机  可是毫无线索
I dumped his phone, but I got nothing.
我也检查了他的车  没有安装导航
Checked his car too, no navigation system.
所以我们还是不知道这个混蛋住在哪里
So we still have no idea where this bastard's living?
皮尔森又没有那么大
Well, Pilsen isn't that big, guys.
我希望大家全员出动
I want boots on the ground.
把达米安和伊莎贝尔的照片散播出去
Circulate photos of Damien and Isabel.
要是在那边有线人  就联系他们
I mean, you've got C.I.'s in the area, get on the phone.
让他们帮忙
Call in a favor.
我们需要尽快找到这些姑娘
We need to find these girls, soon.
你还好吗  心理诊疗怎么样
Hey, how you doing? How's therapy?
不太适合我
Not really my thing.
好吧  如果你不把这事当回事
All right, well, if you're not going to take it seriously
也不准备把它当回事  就告诉我
or even attempt to take it seriously, let me know.
我说真的  因为我得找个新搭档
For real, because I need to find a new partner.
这个人有很多房产
This guy, he owns a lot of houses.
把它们租给皮条客  毒贩
Rents them out to pimps, dealers.
然后从中抽成
He gets a cut of the action.
-有名字吗  -我知道他
- You got this guy's name? - I know of him.
有六个姑娘
There's six girls out there.
被关了起来  生命垂危  这是做好事
In trouble, locked up. You'd be doing a good thing.
我不是想逞什么英雄
I ain't in this to be no hero.
我只是说  这不是我们的一般流程
I'm just saying, this isn't our typical deal.
好吧  我可以帮你问到他的名字
All right, look, I can get the guy's name.
问题是  我的线人是拉丁眼镜蛇的人
Problem is, my connect is a Latin Cobra.
-所以如果你们去抓人...  –你会受牵连
- So if you hit the house-- - You could get burnt.
或者丧命
Or get dead.
你是说劳尔有线索
So you're saying Raul has a lead,
可你却告诉他不要追查
but you told him not to chase it?
你想想看
Okay, think about it.
劳尔问他的拉丁眼镜蛇线人地址
Raul asks his Latin Cobra connect for the address.
然后五分钟之后我们去搜查房子
And then we hit the house five minutes later.
傻子都能猜到我们的线人是谁
It doesn't take a lot of math to figure out who our source is.
我的线人冒险就可以
So it's okay for my C.I. to take on a risk,
你的就不行  你是这个意思吧
but not yours. That's what you're saying?
金  他有老婆还有两个孩子
Kim, he has a wife and two kids.
更别说我已经认识他五年多了
Not to mention I've known him for over five years,
他也给过我超过20个案子的线索
and he's given me over 20 cases.
再说了
And let's be clear.
逼西安娜是你的决定  不是我
It was your choice to push Sienna, not mine.
我知道  那是因为有六个姑娘
I know, because there's six girls out there,
可能被锁在了什么地下室里
probably locked in some basement.
我不可能就这么干等着看她们丧命
And I'm not just going to sit here and let them die.
我和你一样想找到她们
I want to find them as badly as you do,
我也会不择手段找到她们
and I will do everything in my power to make that happen.
不择手段  可是却不能问你的线人
Yeah, everything but ask your informant.
劳尔作为线人的工作  就是提供信息
Raul's job, an informant's job, is to provide information.
他是芝加哥警署的资产
He is an asset of the Chicago Police Department.
不  他是个人
No, he is a person.
也是我的朋友
And he is a friend.
达米安
Damien, hey.
醒醒  芝加哥警署
Wake up, Chicago PD.
我是博伊特警长  这位是奥林斯基警探
I'm Sergeant Voight, this is Detective Olinsky.
我们得问你几个问题
We need to ask you some questions.
律师
Laywer.
看着我
Look at me.
相信我  你要是合作的话
Trust me when I tell you, this will go a lot easier
事情会更轻松
if you cooperate.
你把那些姑娘锁在哪里了
So where are you keeping the girls?
-你觉得我傻吗  -我们已经抓到伊莎贝尔了
- You think I'm stupid? - Well, we already have Isabel.
她爱我
She loves me.
远远超出你们的想象
More than you can possibly imagine.
等你出院
The second you get discharged from here,
就会直接被送进牢房
you're going to jail.
那些姑娘  就会另找皮条客
And those girls, they're going to find a new pimp.
等她们找到了
When they do,
就会轻而易举把你供出来
they will give you up for a slice of pizza.
还好她们被锁起来了
Well, good thing they're locked up.
而且其中一个人有糖尿病
And one of them has diabetes, too.
需要胰岛素
Needs insulin.
她们要是死了  也得算在你的账上
Yeah, well, they die, that just goes on your tab too.
所以帮帮你自己  告诉我们她们的位置
So do yourself a favor, and tell us where they are
这样你就还有机会谈协议
while you still have a chance to make a deal.
好吧  我告诉你们她们在哪儿
All right, I'll tell you where they are...
但你要先给我豁免权
When you offer me total immunity.
在那之前  好走不送
Until then, you can kiss my Colombian ass.
好走不送
Kiss his Colombian ass.
我认识一个人  经历了一场严重的车祸
A guy I know, he had a real bad accident.
摩托车车祸  几年前的事了
A motorcycle accident. It was years ago.
他当时特别疼
I mean, he was in a lot of pain.
最后死在了医院
He ended up dying in the hospital.
但那不是因为他受的伤
But it wasn't from his injuries.
你知道害死他的是什么吗
You know what ended up getting him?
过量吗啡
A morphine overdose.
他们以为是有人
You know, they just figured somebody
不小心按错了数字
punched in the wrong numbers.
这种事经常发生
Happens all the time.
我要是死了  那些姑娘也会死
If--if--if I die, so do the girls.
不会的  我们只会换别的方法找到她们
No, we'll just find them a different way.
-你在虚张声势  -是吗
- You're bluffing. - Am I?
最后机会了  达米安
Last chance, Damien.
我说过了  好走不送
Like I said, kiss my ass.
你看到这张脸了吗  仔细看好了
You see this face? You get a good look at it.
这可是你最后看到的东西了
It's the last thing you're ever going to see.
索托先生
Mr. Soto?
-汉克  -抱歉
- Hank. - Excuse me.
医生
Hey, doc.
我把他交给你了
He's all yours.
那个混蛋根本不在乎
Son of a bitch could care less,
那些姑娘的死活
if these girls live or die.
她们对她来说不是人  而是资产
They're not girls to him. They're assets.
那样的人
A guy like that,
是不会让摇钱树无缘无故地死掉的
he doesn't let a money maker die for no reason.
抱歉
Excuse me.
达米安·索托  是你的病人吗
Damien Soto, is he one of your patients?
是啊  怎么了
Yes, why?
我需要你帮我一个忙
I need you to do me a favor.
帮我在达米安的病房里放一部手机
I want you to leave a cell phone in Damien's room.
就装作是自己忘了
Just pretend you forgot it.
-喂  -是我  达米安
- Hello? - It's me, Damien.
听着  我有麻烦了  大麻烦
Look, man, I'm in a situation, like for real.
我需要现金
I need some cash.
你要干什么
So, what are you looking to do?
-卖点货  -你有多少
- Sell some product. - How many you got?
七个
Seven.
另一个声音属于凯撒·拉莫斯
The other voice belongs to Cesar Ramos.
他是皮尔森的另一个皮条客
He's another pimp working out of Pilsen.
追踪他的位置  跟踪他
Track him down. And follow him.
拉莫斯刚刚停在了潜在目标位置
Ramos just stopped at the possible target location.
准备行动
Get ready to move.
行动
Let's go.
凯撒·拉莫斯  芝加哥警署  转身
Cesar Ramos, Chicago PD. Turn around.
把钳子放下  放下
Drop the bolt cutters. Drop them.
举起手来  下楼梯
Hands in the air, come down the stairs.
好  下来
That's it, come on.
为什么那么看我
Why are you looking at me like that?
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD!
-举起手来  -没事  女士们
- Let me see your hands. - It's okay, ladies.
只要把手举起来  你们就没事
As long as we can see your hands, you're all good.
没事  我们是警察  我们是来帮你们的
It's okay, we're the police. We're here to help.
等等  等等  好  去
Hold on, hold on, okay. Okay, go.
-我负责厨房  -她没事吧
- I got the kitchen. - Is she okay?
楼上
Upstairs!
-没事了  -你没事了  安全
- You're good. - Okay, you're good. Clear!
安全
Clear!
伯吉斯
Burgess.
安全
Clear!
-有希望吗  -她没活下来
- Anything? - She didn't make it.
天啊
Oh, man.
肯定就是她有糖尿病
She must be the diabetic.
我去看看其他人
I'll go check on the others.
找到其他女孩了
We found the other girls.
其中一个死亡
One of them was dead.
因为你的朋友达米安
Because your friend Damien
不肯告诉我们他们在哪里
wouldn't tell us where they were.
我们需要你的帮助来将他定罪
We need your help to convict him.
莉迪亚
Lydia.
你认识莉迪亚  她有糖尿病  需要胰岛素
You know Lydia. She's diabetic, needed insulin.
但是达米安不在乎她的死活
But Damien didn't care if she lived or died.
他不在乎你们任何人的死活
He doesn't care if any of you live or die.
不是的
That's not true.
其实  她说得对
You know what, actually she's right.
你说得对  他在乎  他很在乎
You are right, he did care. He cared a lot.
他想让你们都活着  因为他想卖掉你们
He wanted you all to live because he wanted to sell you.
我们今天录下了他的一通电话
We recorded a call he made today.
是我  达米安
It's me, Damien.
听着  我有麻烦了  大麻烦
Look, man, I'm in a situation, like for real.
-我需要现金  -你要干什么
- I need some cash, so. - What are you looking to do?
-卖点货  -你有多少
- Sell some product. - How many you got?
七个
Seven.
-多少钱  -全部  九万
- How much? - 90K, for all of them.
如果你想  我可以一直放给你听
I can keep playing the tape if you want,
不过确实不好听
but it's not pretty.
告诉我们你知道的  伊莎贝尔
Tell us what you know, Isabel.
他不爱你  伊莎贝尔
He doesn't love you, Isabel.
他假装爱你是为了控制你
He pretends he does so he can control you.
我知道你想相信你们的关系
Look, I know you want to believe in your relationship.
你想心中有希望  我们都是
You want to hold out hope. We all do that.
但我知道  你内心深处知道
But I know that somewhere deep down,
那是个谎言
you know that that is a lie.
我知道是因为我也经历过
I know because I've been there.
我曾爱上过一个人
I was in love with someone once,
但他们并不真爱我
and they didn't really love me.
我一直假装  一直...
And I kept pretending, and I kept...
希望
hoping.
后来我终于受够了
And then eventually I just said enough.
不要继续下去了
God, no more.
虽然很心痛
And it hurt so much.
但是最终我感觉好多了
But you know what? Eventually, I felt better.
直到有一天  我感觉又完整起来了
Until one day, I felt whole again.
现在我唯一后悔的
And now the only thing that I regret
是没有早点那么做
is not doing that sooner.
你是时候说受够了
It's time for you to say enough.
我知道达米安把用来杀希尔维亚的
I know where Damien hid the tire iron
轮胎棒藏在哪里
that he used to kill Sylvia.
你做得很好
You're good.
没事  好了
It's okay. It's good.
做得好  金  你很厉害
Nice job, Kim. You were amazing.
我们有足够证据起诉达米安谋杀了
We have enough to charge Damien with murder,
所以考虑到一切  这个结果算是不错
so not a bad result, all things considered.
我不确定
I'm not so sure about that.
我知道你的意思
Yeah, I know what you mean.
-真的吗  -真的
- You do? - Yeah.
我不...我不后悔保护了自己的线人
Look, I don't--I don't regret protecting my C.I.
一点都不后悔
Not for a second.
但死去的那个女孩莉迪亚
But that girl dying, Lydia?
我得背负那个过完一生
I've got to live with that for the rest of my life.
想知道我们该怎么做  真难
It's hard to figure out what we're supposed to do.
抓坏人  救受害者  保护线人
Get the bad guys, save the victims, protect our C.Is.
如果我不逼迫西恩娜
I mean, if I didn't push Sienna,
或许我们永远都找不到达米安和那些女孩
maybe we'd never find Damien and the girls.
但是西恩娜就可能还活着
But Sienna would still be alive.
有时候真的很难抉择
It's a hard needle to thread sometimes.
更是不可能
More like impossible.
你得相信自己的直觉
You just got to trust your instincts.
对  听从内心  不是规矩
Right. Go with your gut, not the book.
-没错  -知道了
- That's right. - Sweet.
这周末你想一起
Hey, do you want to grab some dinner
去吃个饭吗
or something this weekend?
好  听起来不错
Yeah, that sounds good.
那好
Okay, cool.
好
Cool.
谢谢你这么晚见我
Thanks for seeing me so last minute.
看来你准备聊聊了
Seems like you're ready to talk.
是的
Yeah, I am.
你告诉伊莎贝尔的那个故事
So that story you told Isabel...
-不是说你  -那就好
- That wasn't you. - Good.
-我说真的  -好
- I'm serious. - Okay.
我相信你  但防止你说谎
Yeah, I believe you. But just in case you're lying,
-我想问问...  -亚当  亚当
- I would like you to know that- - Adam, Adam,
我只是想让证人开口  仅此而已
I was just trying to get a witness to flip, simple as that.
没必要回忆过去
There's no need to go backwards, okay?
我现在没那个心情
I'm just-I'm not in the mood.
好吧  如果你想  我们可以去我的住处
Yeah, well, if you want, we could head back to my place.
不是说不回忆过去吗
Talk about going backwards.
那我们可以往前看
Maybe we can move things forward.
不  不会
No, we won't.
为什么  为什么不试试
Why not? Why not give it a shot?
因为
Because...
不知道  我们一起工作
I don't know, we work together.
我们的处境截然不同
We're in totally different places.
好
Okay.
说了刚才的话
Having said that...
我今晚想开心一下了
I feel like having a little fun tonight.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
好
Okay.